ARIEL MANIAGO



2 09659051766

admaniago01@gmail.com

Sitio Undol, Brgy. Camugao, Kabankalan City, Negros Occidental

https://ayiezac.netlify.app/ https://github.com/ayiezac78 https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayie/

PROFILE

Passionate and creative web developer with a proven track record of building responsive and user-friendly websites. Experienced in front-end development technologies such as HTML/CSS, Javascript & ReactJS. Possesses fundamental knowledge in back-end technologies such as MySQL and Laravel. Capable of working independently and collaboratively on certain projects.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Tailwind
- PHP, Laravel, Resftul API, MySQL
- Figma, Adobe Xd, MS Suites
- Team Player & Strong Communication
- · Problem-Solving
- Time Manageable
- Flexible
- Hardware & Network Troubleshooting
- Sales and Marketing
- Customer Service Oriented
- Data Entry & Data Verification

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP TRAINING

KODEGO

Dec 2011 - Apr 2015

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Binalbagan Catholic College

Jun 2011 - Apr 2015

EXPERIENCE

MEDICAL ENCODER

Safeguard DNA Diagnostics, Inc.

Jan 2021 - Feb 2023

- Encoding and uploading patient information and laboratory results onto the laboratory's database through a web application system
- Outbound calls to patients to verify their basic information for contact tracing purposes
- Consolidating and verifying patient information & patient laboratory results in the CDRS report before submitting it to the Department of Health (DOH)

FIELD AUDITOR

GNP1 Marketing

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020

- Conducted field audits to ensure accountability of daily sales personnel and visited stores to audit client interactions
- Conducted outbound call audits of existing clients
- Conducted monthly audits & reports of the warehouse and monitored remittances to ensure accuracy and balance

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

KODEGO - FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

Admin Panel for AWR cLinic Mar 13 - Mar 24, 2023

https://adminawrclinic.netlify.app/

- Tools used: ReactJS, RESTFUL API, Hostinger.com, Netlify, Axios, Tailwind, Postman, Laravel, MySQL
- It's a full-stack web application for Admin Panel of AWR cLinic that manages patient's online appointment's
- Led a team by developing front-end design and creation of RESTFUL API in Laravel & storing directly to the database & also deploying on the cloud server

KODEGO - FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

AWR cLinic Mar 13 - Mar 24, 2023 https://clinicmp2.netlify.app/

- Tools used: ReactJS, RESTFUL API, Render.com, Netlify, Axios, Tailwind
- It's a front-end API-driven web application that focuses on setting patient's online appointment schedule to the clinic.
- Developed front-end design and creation of RESTFUL API to have a CRUD functionalities.

KODEGO - FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

FLOWERPLICITY Feb 1 - Feb 18, 2023 https://flowerplicity.netlify.app/

- Tools used: HTML/CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap 5, Netlify
- It's a static website that focuses on providing a one-stop-shop for flowers
- Led a team in creation of this static website from scratch including wireframe and design

FREELANCE VIDEOGRAPHER

Island Living Channel

Jan - Apr 2019

- · Capturing video clips of various events and scenic locations
- Assisted the Lead Videographer in using various tools for videography

LOAN OFFICER

Negros Women for Tomorrow Foundation

Sep 2016 - Jan 2019

- Processed client's loan applications, reviewing documentation and conducting interviews to determine eligibility and make lending decisions
- Monthly reporting of loan portfolios & loan disbursements
- Conducting weekly meetings at various centers and collecting weekly repayments in different areas